Personalization Thiosh hormone in Laharpathi
peanuts luxury items Mango Bar of the
Universe
Ago O Clock Kanai Helmetino Language
Chokha Helmet No Longer Tu Har Moti Sharma
Awareness Program has been organized and helmets are being
distributed for
free in Agartala
so that there is no injury of any kind
and people wear helmets and first of all I would like to
thank the district administration of Agartala I would like to
thank DGP Mouchak Sir I would like to
thank SP Sir I would like to thank BSP with us
Deepak Sir I would like to thank him wholeheartedly I would like to thank the
entire district administration
with whose cooperation today the
helmet distribution work has been organized in Agartala
and hundreds of helmets are being distributed today.
Now we ICC Bank
sitting MLA
Karo Slogan
[Praise]
[Music]
Look there are eight districts in Tripura and here
we are brother we will do helmet distribution work in every district
in the eighth district so that no one is deprived and can be
saved from road accidents.
ICC Lombard is playing an active role in this.
So that
we can encourage and guide everyone to go there safely
with the cooperation and leadership of the district administration.